http://www.ci-group.com/privacy-policy

HomeAboutServicesAgency ServicesDigitalBranded MerchandiseBranding + DesignAdvertisingWarehousing + FulfillmentExperiential + EventsStrategy + ResearchPrinting + MailingOur WorkBlogCareersContact UsInformation about our Organization and Web SiteProviding Visitors with Anonymous AccessYou can access our Web site’s home page and browse our sites without disclosing your personal data.Automatic Collection of InformationWe automatically log personal data by means such as programming or we link information automatically logged by such means with personal data about specific individuals. We do so for the following purposes:Technical administration of the Web siteCustomer administrationWe use cookies to store personal data. We link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals. All cookies are temporary and are deleted when the browser is closed.Data Collection and Purpose SpecificationWe collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services.We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations.To access the table of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used, please scroll down. We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated in the table below.Children’s PolicyWe do not knowingly collect personal data from children.We take specific steps to protect the privacy of children by:making reasonable efforts to ensure that a parent has authorized the collection of the child’s personal dataPrivacy ComplianceThere are no national laws or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organization.There are no global or regional regulatory or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organization.In order to demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with the above privacy instrument, we are:voluntarily committed to a Self Assessment procedurePrivacy SupportIf you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, contact CI-Group.Personal Data Collected and Purposes for which they are UsedPrimary Personal Data/Business InformationX Volunteered by each Visitor“Not Collected” means that CI-Group does not collect data in any way from web site visitors, public records or bodies, or any private organizations.Primary Personal Data TechnicalAdministration ofthe Web SiteResearch&DevelopmentCustomerAdministrationMarketingTradinginPersonal DataNameXNot CollectedXNot CollectedNot CollectedGenderNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedAddressNot CollectedNot CollectedXNot CollectedNot CollectedE-Mail AddressXNot CollectedXNot CollectedNot CollectedPhone/Fax NumberXNot CollectedXNot CollectedNot CollectedOtherNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedBusiness Information TechnicalAdministration ofthe Web SiteResearch&DevelopmentCustomerAdministrationMarketingTradinginPersonal DataEmployer/ OrganizationNot CollectedNot CollectedXNot CollectedNot CollectedJob TitleNot CollectedNot CollectedXNot CollectedNot CollectedAddressNot CollectedNot CollectedXNot CollectedNot CollectedE-Mail AddressNot CollectedNot CollectedXNot CollectedNot CollectedPhone/Fax NumberNot CollectedNot CollectedXNot CollectedNot CollectedOther Personal Details and Profiling Data TechnicalAdministration ofthe Web SiteResearch&DevelopmentCustomerAdministrationMarketingTradinginPersonal DataPersonal DetailsNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedPhysical DescriptionNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedFamily CharacteristicsNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedEducation and SkillsNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedLifestyle or Personal TastesNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedFinancial ResourcesNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedOtherNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedIdentifiers TechnicalAdministration ofthe Web SiteResearch&DevelopmentCustomerAdministrationMarketingTradinginPersonal DataOn-Line IdentifiersXNot CollectedXNot CollectedNot CollectedFinancial IdentifiersNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedIdentifiers Assigned by Public BodiesNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedBiometrics IdentifiersNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedOtherNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot CollectedNot Collected
